The Milky Way turns in the sky.
In the human world...
The curtains fall in the human world.
Stars
exist beyond the Milky Way.
The departed souls on earth
will eventually become stars,
guarding their loved ones.
Then will my father
also be watching me from the sky?
Perhaps.
He is the brightest one.
No matter how the stars change,
I will be just like him,
guarding you.
Really?
The Big Dipper is my witness.
Then can you tell me
about my father?
What do you want to know?
Anything.
I know too little about his life.
Your father,
he was a warrior who guarded the border.
He fought alongside me
on the battlefield.
With countless military achievements,
he was a true hero.
I knew it.
I knew my father
wasn't like what they said.
He must have been a great hero.
Yes.
Then,
should I call you Uncle?
If I hadn't met you this time...
Just call me by my name.
Just now,
who was chasing you?
Some thieves.
Probably because of my identity.
After my father passed away,
I was adopted into Prince Ling's Manor
as a foster daughter.
Prince Ling's Manor?
How do they treat you?
Very well.
They even
betrothed me to the young master of the manor.
My lord.
I, Ling Ao, son of Prince Ling, pay my respects.
Wait.
I am but an ordinary man.
No need for formalities.
Thank you, sir, for saving Tang'er.
Take good care of her.
I will.
Please.
Will we have a chance to meet again?
If you encounter danger,
blow this flute,
and I will appear.
Xingcan.
I don't need comfort.
Whatever decision you make,
just go for it.
I'm here for you.
You,
come here.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault Uncle Gu got hurt.
If apologies worked,
what would we need the police for?
I was a coward before,
so I didn't dare to step forward.
Now I want to give Uncle Gu
and you an explanation,
and also give myself one.
Okay.
Then from now on,
you do whatever I say.
Understood?
Okay.
Okay, I got it.
Since the problem is clear now,
next,
we must go all out.
Father.
We're here.
We meet again, Miss Gu.
Hello, Uncle.
Where are you from, Miss Gu?
Uncle, I'm a local.
What do your parents do?
My mother passed away from illness when I was very young.
I grew up depending on my father.
But on the day I got into law school,
my dad
passed away in an accident.
Why have I never heard you mention this?
It's all in the past.
You are a strong girl.
Ling Ze,
why did I hear
that you're still using that troublemaking female streamer?
Father,
the company is training newcomers now.
That female streamer still has some traffic.
I plan to stop using her after drawing the traffic.
Make her pay a price
to let the subordinates know
that betraying the Ling family will not end well.
Understood, Father.
You two should hurry up with your matter.
Okay.
What matter of ours?
Father
agreed to our marriage.
That's really great.
Mom, let me help you.
It seems
Hao Zhenshi was right.
Ling Hengsheng is the mastermind behind all the evil deeds.
Ling Ze is just an executor.
I have to overthrow the entire Ling family.
How do you open this thing?
You're asking me?
Well...
maybe we should leave professional work
to the professionals.
Did you guys call a locksmith?
Yes, yes, yes. Please come in.
You want to open this lock?
Yes.
I haven't used it for a long time and forgot the password.
This lock...
is too complicated to open.
It'll cost extra.
What do you mean?
We'll pay extra.
As long as you can open it.
Pay extra?
Alright.
Look at you.
Brother, let me help you.
Sure.
Come here.
Brother, I want to be like you in the future
and run the whole company.
Okay.
Here,
hold it.
Right.
Here.
It hurts.
What's wrong? Let me see.
What's wrong?
How are you watching the child?
Here, let me see.
Mom, Lingyang just...
Lingyang came to help
and accidentally burned himself.
Are you okay, brother?
Come on, help him up.
Are you done yet?
Almost.
Do you even know how to pick it?
I do.
This lock is quite complicated.
It'll take some time.
Don't rush me.
Hey, is it done?
No, this guy is too slow.
Are you crazy?
We are almost done here.
Leave within 10 minutes.
Remember to restore the scene.
Don't leave any traces.
It's open.
What... What are you doing?
What exactly do you do?
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I didn't keep a close eye on my brother today.
It's okay.
Yangyang was just being careless.
Well,
as for Father,
he won't blame you.
He's just mad right now. He'll be fine in a few days.
You should head back now.
Okay.
We'll come see you another day.
Goodbye, Auntie.
Take care.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
Go... go home.
It's none of your business what I do.
Open it right now.
I'm highly suspicious of your identities right now.
If you don't explain clearly, I'll call the police immediately.
Cut the crap.
Open it right now.
Impossible.
Do you want to go for another walk?
It's the weekend, after all.
I'm a bit tired.
Let's just go home.
Let's go.
Hurry, they're back.
That was fast.
You guys...
What are you doing?
Give me back my phone.
We are not bad people.
You act like this and say you're not bad guys.
Let go.
Want a drink?
How about
we go out and find a place to drink?
Sorry, sorry.
Let's drink at home.
Lingze, wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'll go change first.
Okay.
What's going on?
Why haven't you left yet?
I just used my power.
I need to rest for a while.
What happened to them?
They are fine.
Xingcan.
Did you get it?
No.
Forget it. We'll find another chance.
You need to leave now.
I'll find a way to cover you.